https://www.frankmayer.com/privacy-policy/

CONTACT
Privacy PolicyPrivacy Policy and Security Statement of Frank Mayer and Associates, Inc.This privacy policy discloses the privacy practices for www.frankmayer.com. This privacy policy applies solely to information collected by this website. It will notify you of the following:What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the website, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.Information Collection, Use, and SharingWe are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to reply to your contact form submission.Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to reply to your contact form submission, or changes to this privacy policy.Your Access to and Control Over InformationYou may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number given on our website:See what data we have about you, if any.Change/correct any data we have about you.Have us delete any data we have about you.Express any concern you have about our use of your data.SecurityWe take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.While we use best practices for online and server security to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.Our Policy for Protecting Your Online PrivacyThis website uses Google Analytics to help analyze how users use the site. The tool uses “cookies,” which are text files placed on your computer, to collect standard Internet log information and visitor behavior information in an anonymous form. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the website (including IP address) is transmitted to Google. This information is then used to evaluate visitors’ use of the website and to compile statistical reports on website activity for Frank Mayer and Associates, Inc.We will never (and will not allow any third party to) use the statistical analytics tool to track or to collect any Personally Identifiable Information (POI) of visitors to our site. Google will not associate your IP address with any other data held by Google. Neither we nor Google will link, or seek to link, an IP address with the identity of a computer user. We will not associate any data gathered from this site with any Personally Identifiable Information from any source, unless you explicitly submit that information via a fill-in form on our website.LinksThis website may contain links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of these other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of every linked website as their privacy policies may differ from ours. This privacy statement applies solely to the Frank Mayer and Associates, Inc. website. Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) PolicyThis website is not directed to children under 13 years old. The policy of Greater Milwaukee Foundation is to NOT knowingly try to collect any personal information from children under 13, including “individually identifiable information,” as defined by the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA). If you are under 14 years of age, you should leave the website without filling out any of the forms on this website or otherwise providing any information about yourself. If Greater Milwaukee Foundation would knowingly collect personal information from children under 13, it would do so in accordance with COPPA.UpdatesOur Privacy Policy may change from time to time and all updates will be posted on this page.If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately using the contact information below:Frank Mayer and Associates, Inc.1975 Wisconsin Ave.Grafton, WI 53024Phone: 855-294-2875
We use cookies to ensure that we give you the best experience on our website. If you continue to use this site we will assume that you are happy with it.Ok
